everythingy.com 2008-06-18

# Privacy Policy

Everythingy.com is committed to respecting and protecting your personal privacy. Our privacy policy is succinctly explained below. 

Questions regarding our privacy policy should be directed to:

General Counsel  
Everythingy.com  
c/o Vested Ventures, Inc.  
1 Saint Louis Place  
Buffalo, NY 14202 

* * *  
  
**What Does the Everythingy.com Privacy Policy Cover?**  
  
This privacy policy applies to web pages ending in Everythingy.com that contain a link to this privacy policy at the bottom of the web page.

Inclusion of the Everythingy.com logo at the top of a web page does not necessarily mean that this privacy policy applies. Be sure to check the URL that you link to from Everythingy.com web pages to determine whether this privacy policy applies. If you have any questions about this, contact us at privacy-support.

 **Back To Top**

* * *  
  
**What Information Does Everythingy.com Collect From You?**  
  
You can visit our site and use most of our services without having to tell us who you are or reveal any personally identifiable information to us. There are, however, a few instances where we do collect personally identifiable information in order to fulfill your request. 

Whenever you visit Everythingy.com, our web server logs automatically receive and record anonymous information from your web browser including your IP Address, Everythingy.com cookie information, the Everythingy.com page(s) you request, the time spent on each web page and any search terms you query. 

Everythingy.com uses this anonymous information to customize your experience on our site, to show you more relevant advertising messages, and to improve our services in general. For example, when you use Everythingy.com's Toolbar, Everythingy.com can collect aggregate information such as the web pages visited and the time spent on each page. This information allows other users to benefit from the quality searches you perform, ultimately receiving the most relevant, pertinent information. We ordinarily do not attempt to link this information to a specific person. 

**Back To Top**

* * *  
  
**Do Any Third Parties Receive or Collect Your Information Through Everythingy.com?**  
  
In the few instances where Everythingy.com collects personally identifiable information, Everythingy.com will not share it with other companies or individuals unless:

We have your permission to share the information; or

We need to share your information with certain third parties with which we have a business relationship in order to provide a product or service you have requested. Unless we tell you otherwise, these third parties do not have the right to use your personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to deliver your requested product or service; or  

We are responding to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; or-

If Everythingy.com is acquired by another company whether through merger or purchase of its stock or all or substantially all of its assets, we will share the information with the acquiring company. 

Furthermore, Everythingy.com will not sell or disclose your personally identifiable information as customer lists to anyone. Nor will we share with anyone personally identifiable information about you that is of medical, financial or sexual nature.

Everythingy.com shares some of the user information, such as user trends, search language, and time of day with third parties that may set and access cookies on your computer. Other advertisers or advertising services may set cookies but this information is not shared with Everythingy.com nor is it personally identifiable information. 

None if these third parties nor any other advertiser or advertising service, receives personally identifiable information from Everythingy.com. However, certain advertisements or contests you see on our site may provide for the collection of personally identifiable information. Such information is never shared with Everythingy.com. 

**Back To Top**

* * *  
  
**What Security Measures Are in Place to Protect Your Information?**  
  
Everythingy.com operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your user data. 

Only certain employees have access to the information you provide us.  

**Back To Top**

* * *  
  
**How Will You Be Notified if Everythingy.com Changes This privacy policy?**  
  
Everythingy.com updates this policy from time to time. If we are going to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our databases, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. Bear in mind that the only way to ensure your personal privacy whenever you are on the Internet is to make sure your browser is configured so that you are alerted to all cookies. 

**Back To Top**

* * *  
  
**Your Questions or Suggestions Regarding This privacy policy.**  
  
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy or the practices of this site, please contact us at privacy-support, or for New York residents, contact <http://www.oag.state.ny.us/internet/internet.html>.  

Policy updated and effective date: May 13, 2008

* * *
